...started to kind of get back on track, and
we had a conversation about, you know,
do we actually want to do this?
And it just felt like the right time.
So in March of 2012,
we started JM2 Architecture,
and there were probably about
eight clients that we had.
And we got our big break in
April or May, when Amneal
Pharmaceuticals was doing a large
400,000 square foot addition
to their existing facility in Brookhaven,
and John and I were just operating out of a
bedroom with one computer, one printer,
a little gray buffet table from Home
Depot as our conference room table,
and this project came along, and we
were under crazy deadlines. It forced us to
work nearly around the clock in the
beginning, because it was a very
high-profile project, and it had
every local official, politician, everybody
wanted to be a part of this. We were a
lead project. We were adding 750 jobs.
It was a $130 million project, so
there was a lot of attention on it.
It was a very high-profile project, and for us,
right out of the gate, we had to do
everything possible to make it happen.
And I'll never forget the construction
manager, the late Jack Hulka, said,
"James, how long is it going to take
you to do site plans?"